Never talk to strangers.
The Black Phone is a horror, thriller film directed by Scott Derrickson.
Finney Blake, a shy but clever 13-year-old boy, is abducted by a sadistic killer and
trapped in a soundproof basement where screaming is of little use.
When a disconnected phone on the wall begins to ring, Finney discovers that
he can hear the voices of the killer’s previous victims.
And they are dead set on making sure that what
happened to them doesn’t happen to Finney.
Finney, played by Mason Thames.
Gwen, played by Madeleine McGraw.
The Grabber, played by Ethan Hawke.
Terrence, played by Jeremy Davies.
Detective Wright, played by E. Roger Mitchell.
Detective Miller, played by Troy Rudeseal.
Black Phone 2 is a 2025 American supernatural horror film
directed by Scott Derrickson who co-wrote it with C.
Robert Cargill.
It serves as a sequel to The Black Phone (2021), is the second feature film
and third overall installment in the Black Phone franchise.
The film stars Mason Thames, Madeleine McGraw, Jeremy Davies, and Ethan Hawke reprising
their roles from the first film, with Demián Bichir also joining the cast.
The story sees siblings Finney and Gwen, along with their friend Ernesto, head to a winter youth camp to uncover a
mystery regarding the first victims of the Grabber, whose ghostly presence now haunts the camp.
Black Phone 2 premiered at Fantastic Fest on September 20, 2025, and was
released in the United States by Universal Pictures on October 17.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and has
grossed $132 million worldwide with a budget of $30 million.
The film explores themes of mask, small town, child
abuse, dreams, sibling relationship.
The tone is dark and intense.